NGUYỄN VIỆT HÙNG

.NET DEVELOPER



hnv2311@gmail.com

23/11/2001





PROFILE _____

.NET Developer with 9+ months of experience developing web, and web API using .NET Core and MS SQL, MySQL. Understanding of the software development process. Bringing leadership strength and the ability to listen to and understand customer requirements

___EXPERIENCE ____

Jan 2024 - Now

Build Online foood Ordering and Traffic Management System for P&B (Công ty cổ phần thực phẩm P&B)

- Collaborated with P&B's internal team to define project requirements and deliverables
- Developed a robust RESTful API using .NET 8, handling over 1,000 requests per minute with minimal latency
- Managed the deployment of the application to P&B's production environment using **Docker containers**
- Developed a Flutter mobile application for P&B's delivery Staff

Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

FPT Software Co. Intern .NET

- Analyze existing application code, writing unit test, and debugging application
- · Build and deploy the system to Azure cloud

_ EDUCATION ____

Dec 2019 - May 2024

FPT University HCM

Bachelor of Software Engineering

_ SKILLS __

Programming languages:

• C#, Java, Dart

Framework:

• .Net. basic Flutter

Database:

• SQL (SQL Server), MySQL

Cloud:

Basic Azure, AWS

Others:

- GitHub, Unit Test, Redis
- Linux OS, Docker

__ACTIVITY_____

Write and share articles about technology and effective techniques on my Facebook group

https://www.facebook.com/groups/ hocduthu

PERSONAL PROJECT

TsdDelivery WebAPI

Aug 2023 - Dec 2023

Brief: A system that allows customers and drivers to book and receive orders for goods transportation. Techs: C#, ASP.Net core 7 WebApi, Entity Framework, SQL Server

Other Techs: Jwt, Redis cache, Hangfire, Routing API, Momo payment, ZaloPay payment, PayPal, Azure.

URL Source code: https://github.com/viethung23/TsdDelivery

CERTIFICATE

Software Development Lifecycle Coursera @

Web Design for Everybody: Basics of Web Development & Coding Coursera@

Linux Fundamentals Coursera @

Academic Skills for University Success Coursera@

Computer Communications Coursera@